[Music]
uh
oh
[Music]
hello everybody and welcome to this
extraordinary emergency session of the
ask Abit show I hope you're all doing
very well and this obviously is in the
context of the US election result Donald
Trump has won he is the
47th president elect of the United
States and he's going to take power in
January January 21 or something like
that somewhere around that time so
that's what this is about that's why
this emergency live stream uh I am doing
it and I look forward to your questions
what we have to understand is this the
United States is the most important
nation in the world it's the most
powerful political geopolitical Imperial
entity that has ever existed in human
history and its impact on human history
is going to be felt for centuries if not
a couple of thousand years if not more
that's how important the US is and we
have to pay attention to this nation and
we have to understand this nation and
the fact is that the US is an extremely
misunderstood nation very few people
understand it properly and that's why
I'm I'm announcing a new podcast called
understanding America which I'm going to
start releasing from next week onwards
it's going to be a once a week uh
podcast one episode per week it's going
to have at least 100 episodes so it's at
least a two-year project at at minimum
and I'm going to take a really deep dive
in each episode on some on one
particular aspect of American History
more or less chronologically so it's
going to be a big project it's going to
start next week the understanding
America podcast on this channel so this
is the announcement I look forward to
having you on that but yeah today we are
talking about the election result and
let's take a look at who all is there on
the live stream let me see uh I can see
a whole lot of people let's see we have
geopolitical dub AES digpal SS kjan Pari
brain tagi Ashish Karan aush Pand BB
onion duck agent hin um Zeus Zeus 1V
zubon is arbit Pak rudra omik Vin Mishra
bishwajit
B pray Paul janavi rala ainash Guru Kant
Muk harsh Singh
bumar the L abishek dedi dedi Tushar
Kori Banda Panda gopinath
bisra Chan desand a aush Pand again
sarank Kad SG Gupta m
Priyanka javia hello alok swapnesh
shalar Mr B B sub sha adwa Naga NAD GAA
guide Realms V noop Malaki n Abhijit cha
light r karma somia R
RMS and a whole lot of other people so
thank you all for being on the on the
live stream and let's take the questions
let's take the
questions uh okay let's let's let's
begin here Noob Gamers taggy says what's
going to happen with Bangladesh
Bangladesh is
yes it's it's a matter of immediate
concern for us in the Indian
subcontinent isn't isn't it Bangladesh
and the Biden Harris regime has recently
very quite recently carried out a regime
change operation in Bangladesh they as
we know I'm sure everyone's aware they
removed the democratically
constitutionally elected shik Hina
government from Power he was outed she
was forced to leave the country by the
by the Bangladesh military and now
there's a puppet regime in place a
completely undemocratic completely
unelected completely unconstitutional
puppet regime is in place with this
fellow called Muhammad yunus as the as
the face of the papet regime it's
actually the Bangladesh military that's
running the show and the Bangladesh
military obviously has a has a much
larger Master out there which we all
understand is the US it's this has been
coming it's been a long time coming
coming because you spoke about this in
the Years coming up to the actual coup
so that's a situation that's a context
in which this question has been asked
what will happen with Bangladesh because
just I mean less than a week before the
the election result which is today uh
Trump had tweeted this shall we let
let's find his TW I don't I don't think
it'll be easy to find his tweet uh
there'll be a lot of Tweets in in the
way but he essentially tweeted about
Bangladesh and he said that he strongly
condemns the barbaric attacks on the
Hindus and other minor minties in
Bangladesh and so on and so forth and he
also spoke about uh the need for India
and the US to work together and he said
that if elected he will you know resume
cooperation kind of like in in some
words he said that with with his good
friend n and so on so forth so that was
a deal so he actually was one of the
very few world leaders to condemn
strongly what's happening in Bangladesh
the programs against Hindus and
minorities also because you got to speak
about them but mainly against Hindus and
also against Buddhists and so on that's
been happening ever since this Muhammad
Yus person this regime came to power
they have been going after the Hindus
Bangladesh has once again become East
Pakistan and this was all done by the by
the Biden Harris
regime and the objective is to encircle
India and so on I've spoken about it at
length I'll not go into that right now
so the question is what happens now
Trump is now going to be the president
January some 21st or so whatever date
onwards so what happens will shika be
brought back to Power will Muhammad Inus
be ousted lots of Indian commentators
are speculating right now on social
media I'll not go into the tweets and
all that but they're speculating that
yeah you know Muhammad unus was be
trembling and all that I disagree
completely Bangladesh East Pakistan is
an extremely valuable asset for the
United States in the Indian
subcontinent why would you give it up
I mean sure uh Trump under under Trump's
leadership the United States may may ask
uh the Bangladeshi regime to go easy on
the Hindus on the minorities and stop
you know genociding them and all that
maybe that'll happen sure I'm sure Mr
Modi will speak with Mr Trump and uh you
know use his influence to uh end the
violence against Hindus to a certain
extent hopefully to a large extent
hopefully completely but beyond that I
don't see anything else happening I
don't think Muhammad Yus will be thrown
out of power and shik will be allowed to
come back absolutely not mark my words
that's not
happening even among
friends you know you need leverage
because in the game of GE politics there
are no real friends I mean you may have
individual friendships between two world
leaders let's say between Donald Trump
and Mr Modi we know that they got along
really well together so there may be an
individual friendship there but this is
geopolitics it's about National interest
I may be your friend but I have my
national interest and you have yours and
we're going to
deal you know deal between the countries
from that perspective our individual
friendship means nothing in that context
that's how it works in
geopolitics and the US is concerned
about uh the
increasingly larger role that India is
playing on the geopolitical stage and
eventually the way the Indian economy is
growing India is going to become a very
large power and that's obviously a
problem that's something they don't want
to see happen that's why they want to
contain India and Bangladesh is an
excellent asset to have in the
subcontinent to contain India to to uh
play a certain part of the role in
containing India so I do not see Donald
Trump uh having the Muhammad yunus
regime ousted and having shik reinstated
that's not going to
happen so Bangladesh not no major change
maybe an easing up on the on of the
violence against Hindus maybe that'll be
curbed to a certain extent once Trump
comes to par but beyond that I don't see
a lot happening uh project K project
cookie land for Christ will
continue that will continue even if
Donald Trump is in power it will still
continue so that's how the game is
played uh transactionally the
relationship will get better but when it
comes to Bangladesh when it comes to
project Kila and man the Manipur
disaster uh not a lot will change that's
how I see it okay next question lots of
questions lots of
questions V Shava says what's my take on
the mizoram chief
Minister's activities in the United
States very
interesting um stuff that's going on so
this uh gentleman I forget his name I
can't pronounce his name Mr L something
uh the chief minister of
mizoram so this gentleman is a
constitutionally uh elected uh
representative of the Indian people
right in the state of mizoram he has
taken an O oath of office and he has
sworn to uphold the Constitution and so
on so forth and the sovereignty National
territorial Integrity Etc of the country
but in the
US he's been making these statements in
which is essentially essentially saying
that we The Zo people the cookie Zoo
people or whatever
see the misos and the Zoomies and the
cookies Etc are the same people so when
it comes to the cookie infiltration
that's happening inside India lacks of
cookies coming into India across the
border a lot of that allegedly is said
to be coming in through mizoram so
Manipur mizoram nagaland Etc the entire
Eastern flank of India we have open an
we've always had an open border policy
with Burma Burma is a friendly nation
has been historically friendly Nation
it's part of the indosphere same culture
Etc so we have no actual issues over
there no territorial disputes also but
now there's a situation there where a
Civil War and
uh and and the cookies this particular
tribal group the cookies they are
actually not even Burmese they don't
speak the Burmese
language they don't practice burmis
culture they have mostly converted to
Christianity or whatever were other
abrahamic religion some of them claim to
be uh Jewish despite being a tribe that
eats Spork which is very interesting
yeah and so the cookies and the misos
are the same people so a whole lot of
this in infiltration is allegedly
happening via mizoram lacks of them are
being brought are being brought in via
the mizoram Burma border allegedly and
then they are routed into they they
pushed into Manipur they not allowed to
settle in mizoram but they pushed into
Manipur to occupy Manipur and that's how
thousands of artificial Villages new
Villages have come up in Manipur
Southern Manipur especially in the past
few years that's the issue so looks like
the mizoram government is kind of
allegedly complicit in what's happening
I mean that's the allegation that's been
that has been made
repeatedly uh off
late okay and these individuals once
they come in they get all the
documentation and all and they
essentially become Indian citizens and
they get more rights and privileges than
the actual indigenous people of Manipur
that's what's happening this is a
disaster absolute
disaster now there's a whole bunch of
cookies who live on the Eastern side of
the Border in Burma there's a whole
bunch of them who have infiltrated into
India and who have settled in who who
are now occupying manipuri territory and
then the kooki there's there's a miso
people as well who live in mizoram same
ethnic group spread across and and a
bunch of them also apparently live in
the Chittagong uh hills region of
Bangladesh so the cookies are currently
fighting three governments they're
fighting the burmes government they're
fighting the Bangladesh government okay
military Civil War kind of situation
Insurgency terrorism activities and they
also doing the same thing terrorism in
Manipur against the Indian government
they are fighting three
nations okay and look this rag tag half-
naked tribal
group how come they are so very well
organized first question secondly very
is this Limitless supply of arms and
ammunition coming from drones they they
they bombed the capital of Manipur via
drones through drones imagine the
capital of an Indian state is is is
under attack by drones drone bombing
incredible how did they get the drones
the technology the noow ETC and who is
organizing them who's providing the
leadership obviously it's it's it's
being done from outside there's a larger
power in play play over here the Puppet
Master
live very far away across the oceans the
other side of the planet so the church
is very much involved in this okay it's
very well known uh so essentially it's
it's project K cookie land for Christ
and the objective is to create a new
nation artificial Christian Nation out
of parts of India Bangladesh and
Burma which parts of India mizoram and
Manipur large parts of these two states
okay okay so this St this artificial
Nation essentially cuts off India's
access to Southeast Asia to Eastern Asia
the same way that Pakistan cuts off
India's access to Western Asia and
Eurasia the same sort of thing so they
want to completely this larger power out
there wants to completely encircle India
imagine the Chinese um string of pearls
on steroids that sort of
thing um so this is that's the context
in which we have to see the activities
of the esteemed chief minister of
mizoram who goes to to to the US and
from US Territory says that we cannot
accept the division of The Zo people and
we are divided across three or four
countries or whatever and we will
reunite and all that and then when he is
asked about this he the statement that
is put out later when this all came and
became a big issue on social media the
statement that's put out is that he's
talking about reunification under under
the context of the Indian or something
that's the kind of excuse he's making
essentially what he's saying that that's
you know that that doesn't really cut it
you know that it's not convincing at all
what if you and and the text of his
speech is actually available on a
government website on an Indian
government website official
website this uh secessionist sentiment
is shared is is is put out proudly on an
Indian government website so that that's
what's happening it is extremely
problematic for us and the real puppet
master behind all of this is the United
States the Deep State the CIA whatever
you want to call it they have had a very
long presence in India's Far East it is
American missionaries Christian
missionaries who converted very very
large parts of the population of the Far
East to Christianity most of nagaland
has lost its culture cultural
Devastation genocide cultural genocide
and conversion to a foreign religion who
did it it was American missionaries who
did it with the blessings of the great
magnificent Mr neru so most of the
christianization and most of the
cultural loss happened after 1947 not
during British times can you imagine
that and you've had American Christian
activity missionary activities in India
for going on for decades you know this
actor Tom
alter who who was a this this american
guy you know blue-eyed guy who speaks
extremely good Udu not Hindi uru well
that guy his parents were American
missionaries so that's the kind of
activities the Americans have been doing
and they they their objective is to
create this new artificial Christian
Nation out of parts of India Bangladesh
and and and uh
Burma uh so this is extremely
concerning and uh the government of
India needs to take this up at various
levels with the United States and first
of all and and that's number two and
that's second but first of all we have
to reign
in the chief minister of mizoram if
required if you know if if he is
indulging in anti-national activities
secessionist activities we should be
sacked if if I mean you know I think
there is enough justification for that
so I think the call has to be taken by
the government of India by the Modi
government but this is extremely
concerning and uh the Puppet Master as
always is uncle
okay okay Ashish says how surprised am I
that Donald Trump has won
well not a lot but it is still
surprising so look I have said this
multiple times on the ask show and
elsewhere that I think it's it was very
likely in my opinion that Kamala Kamala
would win
right but I said and I did say that
Donald Trump will win if he if he has
kissed the ring and what do I mean by
kissing the ring it means getting
aligned aligning politically Etc with
the the entities that actually run rule
the United States which is the entity
that rules the United States I mean
there's somebody who's ruling the United
States it's not Joe Biden it's not
Kamala Harris those two people are
incompetent Joe Biden is well sin or
whatever you want to call it and caral
is she well the the the competence isn't
there right so someone is still running
the United States so that's the whatever
you want to call it you know people use
different names for it uh the defense
military establishment the Deep State
whatever but there is a bunch of
individuals who rule the United States
and that's and that group of individuals
is not an elected group of individuals
let's call it
the Deep State okay whatever you want to
call it
so I said that if Trump kisses The Ring
Of The Deep State then he will be
allowed to win so what does that mean it
means
that they are now convinced they have
been convinced by Trump and his
activities and his actions over the past
year or so during the election campaign
that he is aligned with their overall
big picture agenda for the United States
so the past four years Kamala and Biden
have pushed in several million illegals
into the United States and they have
been settled in all parts of the US they
came in through mostly the southern
border the Texas Mexico border and they
are individuals from all across the
world all illegals all B of passports
but now they probably have voted and the
we still have the situation that Trump
won but now you have several million
illegals who are settled in the US and
it will be very very hard for Trump to
remove them so that is done that's a f
okay uh now what's the agenda of the
deep State I mean they want to expand
their
power if you
are uh a secretive
invisible group of people small group of
people who have a lot of power first of
all you don't want to be exposed you
don't want people to know who you are
secondly you want to consolidate the
power hold on to the power and thirdly
you want to expand the power you want to
be even more
powerful so aligning with that agenda
means Trump has to make them more
powerful the Trump regime wittingly or
unwittingly next four years has to make
the United States essentially more
powerful how do you do that first of
all uh
technologically the us through a I and
space
exploration is already in pole position
in the next four years it'll probably
surpass Every Other Nation and leave
every Other Nation far
behind via its technological
advancements a lot of that has to do
with Elon Musk and Sam Alman and the AI
companies Microsoft and open Ai and
whatever else perplexity who is run by
an Indian and so on so you have ai you
have space
exploration before the Trump
Administration is done next four years
you will have Elon musk's rockets and
whatever else on
Mars so he's going to send Elon Musk is
going to send the Starship multiple
Starship uh launches to Mars in the next
two years there's there's a launch
window every roughly what's I think
every 26 months or so because the two
planets they this they orbit the Sun at
different different there are different
orbital periods right so it's every once
in 26 months or so that there's a
certain amount of time where you have
the optimum launch window to launch a
spacecraft for Mass from here from Earth
so I think it's going to be in sometime
in the next two years so Elon mask is
going to launch a bunch of Starships the
gigantic one that he has the biggest
rocket ever made and two years after
that he's going to send humans if
everything goes well so
before 2028 29 you probably will have if
things go well humans on Mars okay and
that's going to make the US like
Untouchable in the space of in in in the
in the context of space exploration so
that makes the US way more powerful than
every Other Nation that's good for the
Deep state right secondly the economy
will stabilize the Trump will stabilize
the economy is going to yeah it's not
going to be very difficult for him to
stabilize the economy it'll take a
couple of years for things to go well
but it'll happen so the US economy will
be stabilized uh the US will disengage
from Ukraine most likely and and pile on
even more pressure on China and probably
India as well to some extent so all of
that will uh
uh consolidate and extend us power uh
Trump will go hard on NATO and the other
European nations as well very
transactional president you know the art
of the deal and all that so overall the
Trump
Administration its agenda is kind of in
line with the
long-term uh and short-term plans of the
deep State whoever the Deep state is so
I and and I'm sure that Elon Musk is
also very much aligned with the Deep
State agenda and all that and so are the
other uh invincibles or whoever that
team of people that Elon Musk that that
Trump has created right there's Trump
there's JD van his vice president there
is Elon Musk obviously there is Joe
Rogan the podcast guy there is Dana
White the MMA guy then there's vivak
ramaswami there's telsey gabard um who
else do we have on this team I'm sure
I'm missing out a couple of people but
you get the picture this there's Kennedy
RFK Jr and whoever else so these people
will be on the on on board the Trump
Administration in some way or the other
Elon Musk definitely and they're going
to make the US I mean tremendously more
powerful than what it is today that that
all is good for for the long-term
short-term Etc agenda of the deep state
so and KLA Harris and and would never
have been able to do that so I think
this is a period of time in which the US
undergo some kind of set it consolidates
power and then 28 they'll see do we get
the Democrats back or do we get the
Republicans and give them another shot
because Trump will be done two terms and
you're done so yeah that's the kind of
thing it is so I'm not tremendously
surprised it's actually good for the
Deep state to have someone like Trump
for a for a period of four years uh so
yeah that's how I see it okay okay other
questions other
questions okay Muhammad is smile says uh
let me have a sip of coffee now that
President Trump is you can
win okay now that President Trump will
be in office will terrorism in Manipur
settle down I just kind of took this
question but yeah let's briefly address
it again I don't think terrorism in
Manipur will will
subside or reduce to a very large extent
I think project k k land for Christ will
continue it will continue Full Steam
onward and um yeah so I I I don't see
that happening
unfortunately because look the objective
is to contain India unless
India you know accepts to
voluntarily stop growing its economy
they're going to do this and obviously
India under Modi or whoever will never
accept that let's cut down on our
economic growth and and remain mired
inan growth rates 4% 5% per year that's
not going to happen so I don't see
terrorism in Manipur going down and
Trump whether he likes it or not it's
going to happen some things Trump won't
be able to control like what's what the
CIA does what the US deep state does in
various Nations regime CH and all
that what Trump will be able to control
is whether you start a new war or not
somewhere so Trump has always been
anti-war he was the first president in
in decades who did not start a new war
and probably he may not start a new war
during this next four-year term but
regime change operations
certainly could happen and what's
happening in Manipur unfortunately we
will have to solve it we can't wait for
the Americans to benevolently turn off
the tap on the on the terrorism that's
not going to happen so we will have to
we'll have to find a
solution vickram geopolitical asks a
great question how Will trump handle the
anti-india and khalistani elements
residing in the US um when it comes to
the anti-india elements khalistani
terrorists khalistani supporters Etc who
reside in the US um Trump May kind of uh
control their activities to some extent
he may have them tone down their
activities to some extent perhaps
possibly
uh to whatever extent he can he may do
it so what you may see is that whatever
is happening from us
soil may may simmer down during the
Trump Administration but whatever's
happening whatever anti-india activities
Etc are happening from Canadian soil
from UK territory from Australian
territory etc those want stop because
technically these are separate Nations
and they are independent Sovereign
Nations technically we all know that's
fiction that they're all wasal of the us
we know that we know that but the world
doesn't know that right only those who
watch the ask sure know
that so uh so that that will
continue
uh when it comes to Justin
Trudeau um look Trudeau may not win the
next election perhaps that's a
possibility but whoever wins the next
election in Canada let's see it's Pi or
whoever it is it won't make too much of
a difference on the act when it comes to
the activities of the uh anti-india
forces and khalistani terrorists who are
Canadian citizens right um so Trump may
have the anti-india activity on us soil
simmered on to a certain extent but not
from other countries and uh yeah you
can't expect him to do too much because
it's it's it's a form of Leverage they
have against us any and all Leverage is
valuable because you can use it in
negotiations and to affect the outcomes
of negotiations and treaties and all
that so why would you give it up
entirely okay
um let us
see okay geopolitical dub says Trump won
the election
but will Mr Trump be allowed to take the
oath of office I think he will I think
he will uh I don't see any uh impediment
to him uh taking the oath of office he
has won a clear majority he won won the
popular vote he has won the Electoral
College votes as well he has a majority
on from both perspectives so I don't
think there's any constitutional or
legal angle which could uh help the
Democrats or whoever else to prevent him
from taking office so I don't see that
going to be a
problem
okay okay mythical Sati says can there
be other assassination attempts on the
new poas what are the impact of this
election on other major
countries uh well look I'd rather not
speculate about assassination attempt
and all that okay this is something that
happens that is deeply illegal activity
it it's very I mean no Nation can
tolerate such such things
and uh so I don't know look I how will I
know if there's an assass there's going
to be more assassination attempts I
think you should ask astrologers about
that
uh when is it likely that a certain
world leader could face assassination
attempts it's likely that a world leader
has a higher probability of facing an
ass attempt either when he's deeply
unpopular in his own country or he
is upsetting the Apple card and rocking
the boat so to say uh Visa the real
rulers of the country the the Deep state
or he is doing something that makes
other countries very uncomfortable very
powerful countries it harms their
interests these are the roughly broad
scenarios in which you could have
assassination attempts on
a world leader from any country when it
comes to the United States it's very
very difficult to imagine another
country being able to carry out or even
attempting being even able to attempt an
assassination attempt on a US president
it's unheard of it it want I don't think
there's any instance in history where
that's happened um so then the only
scenario in which an assassination
attempt on a US president can happen is
either if he is deeply unpopular broadly
and deeply unpopular among the populists
or if he is doing something that is
detrimental to the interests of the deep
State President John F Kennedy comes to
mind in that second context so in such
scenarios you could imagine that there's
a higher likelihood of there being an
assassination attempt on a sitting
president that's what I can tell you so
in those scenarios you could have such a
thing that's all speculative that's all
hypothetical that we're not talking
about any Act ual actuals away here okay
uh what's the what are the impacts of
this election on other major countries
oh uh there's going to be lots of
impacts on major
countries so let's let's go one by one
with Visa various
countries who's going to be happy with
this election with with with the fact
that Donald Trump returns to power first
of all India is going to be happy
because the past four years the
Democrats the Biden Harris regime has
piled on the agony on India piled on the
misery on
India um
so India is going to be happy Mr Modi is
going to be happy for sure okay things
will improve between India and the us
transactionally at least well look even
when Trump was President you had the uh
the Delhi riots Etc which were allegedly
carried out by
deep
state so Trump may not be able to
prevent that but overall transactionally
the the the relationship will improve so
India will be
happy the relations will improve uh
Israel will be happy the Democrats have
historically of late been extremely
antagonistic towards Israel the Obama
Netanyahu relationship immediately comes
to mind right so now the Israelis will
be happy nanahu will be happy who else
do with think will be happy Muhammad bin
Salman will be happy I mean the yeah so
it will
be it'll be good overall better for him
as well who's going to be unhappy with
this uh Xi Jinping it doesn't make too
much of a difference for him whether
it's Biden in power or Trump in power
the us is going to pile on the heat on
China so good for us
India uh it gives us options Visa V
China it gives us Leverage when it comes
to our dealings with China good for us
so Xi Jinping won't be happy China won't
be happy Iran won't be happy remember
solmani kasum solman Donald Trump had
him assassinated the the Iranian General
so Iran won't be happy Iran will face
more heat the Israelis will feel feel
emboldened now by the election of
President Trump that they will have more
of a free hand in dealing with uh
dealing against Iran
so Iran will be unhappy about
this Putin will be
happy so the impact of this election
once Trump comes to power is that Trump
look Trump trump hates hates wastage of
money he wants a good deal in everything
and this incredible expenditure the US
has incurred since 22 since 2022 on the
Ukraine war it's a huge waste of
taxpayer money American taxpayer money I
see Trump shutting that down what does
that
mean what happens if the US shuts down
military aid and financial assistance to
Ukraine it means zilinski is
toasted so uh zalinski needs
to very rapidly come up with lots of
various options uh next phase of life
okay he needs to get out of Kev soon
sooner rather than than later because
once Trump pulls the plug the war is
over the US will disengage from the
Ukraine mess it's going to be a huge uh
game changer for Europe as well for NATO
for for the EU a lot will change there
so there's going to be a lot of concern
in the U in the EU right now and in NATO
about what Trump's new policies are
going to be like so a lot will change
when it comes to Pakistan not a lot will
change when it comes to Bangladesh not a
lot will change when it comes to uh the
Asia Pacific Indo Pacific region uh
Trump will push India to be more uh
active in the quad Etc that will happen
so once again see right now we are
seeing this India China relationship
getting better uh Trump will not be
happy with that and he will try to
prevent that from happening so there's
going to be pressure on India certainly
but overall things will get better for
India when it comes to Canada well
Canada doesn't doesn't really matter the
UK doesn't really matter uh the five
eyes Nations apart from the US don't
matter so all that in Africa
um well things will go on kind of the
way they have but the the US Russia
relationship May kind of get better kind
of to some extent and the North Korea
thing will also kind of improve
because Trump and Kim Jong-un are kind
of friends they were friends to some
exent and so on so lots of things lots
of geopolitic
relations will get recalibrated for sure
so a lot is going to change and very
rapidly too once he assumes office
Trump
okay John V oh thank you thank you so
much
ma'am okay uh yeah yes right okay so how
will the Trump government benefit India
now they will ease up the pressure on
India look the question then is what's
the pressure we have been facing in
India uh from from the
US what's happened has already happened
that won change so the regime change in
Pakistan the out of Imran Khan and the
new government us Pro US Government
coming in which happened in 2022 that
will not change the regime change in
Bangladesh want change but what will
change is uh the other things the
American and the project K giland will
also not change but uh the relationship
between the two leaders will be
different it will be less hostile less
tense less patronizing more
transactional but friendlier warber um
all the the the barrage of
anti-india sentiments expressed in the
western media May kind of change to a
certain extent May they'll tone it down
perhaps to a certain
extent um the sanctions that have been
imposed on India last week just a week
or so ago less than a week ago by the
Biden regime
that may be
Revisited maybe Trump will be willing to
perhaps uh withdraw those
sanctions um Trump will want India to
buy more us equipment arms ammunition
all of that so that could be beneficial
to India to a certain extent and Trump
will be very very strongly he was very
very harsh against China he started the
trade and tariff war against China he is
going to take that to the next level
most likely or at least continue what's
already going on
so China will definitely face if not the
same amount of heat even perhaps even
more heat from the US which is good for
India it gives us leverage against
China um so overall the the uh the
attitude of the Trump regime towards
India is going to be more positive more
friendly than the Biden regime ever has
been uh I remember the first time Mr
Modi went to the Went to went to
Washington uh after Biden and and Kamala
to took power I remember he was he was
addressing the press and Kamala was next
to him and he started lecturing him
about human rights and freedom of
religion and all that in front of the
press that sort of treatment won't
happen so overall I see the relationship
getting better in a nuanced way uh India
won't face that much heat it will be
beneficial to India uh especially when
it comes to uh our relationship ship
with China it may give us more leverage
against China but uh on the other hand
we will be pressurized to kind of
distance ourselves from Moscow which is
not good for us we want to be friendly
with everyone so it's going to be
nuanced it's definitely going to be
nuanced but overall it's going to be
better for India it's going to be better
for the world uh so time will tell but
overall I see it getting
better
okay uh thank you sir thank you deep
G ishan says will there be any change in
the India Canada relationship I don't
see too much of a change happening in
the India Canada Canada relationship uh
Canada obviously we know is a us wasal
it's a us uh Clan State and uh the
change that you will see will be in the
US India relationship um there the US it
doesn't serve their interests in making
the India Canada relationship
better uh
Trudeau as long as he is in power the
relationship between India and Canada
will remain the
same uh Trudeau cannot afford to go back
on what he has already done he cannot
afford alienating his uh terrorist
constituency the khalistani con
constituency he can't afford to alienate
them no political party in Canada can
afford to alienate the the khalistani
constituency right uh so Canada will
remain Canada not not a lot will change
if
here P comes to power even then I don't
see a lot changing because even he will
have to appease the khalistanis right
the so the Canadian citizens there is
not such thing as khalistan by the way
it's a fictitious La La Land it only
exists in Canada so we can uh request
the Canadian government to give those
individuals a piece of territory and
they can call it kistan but I don't see
any any major change when it comes to
the India and
relationship uh okay interesting
question not about the elections but
yeah it's it's geopolitically it's it's
it's a topic I've spoken about so let's
take
this so the question is by yaj Kumar
what do I think about the development
that's recently happened in the British
Indian Ocean
territory uh well now I do do we
remember what the British Indian Ocean
territory is do I have to go to the map
uh let me go to the map uh very quickly
very rapidly where's the map where's the
map let me put that on the screen I only
have one screen here today I usually
have two screens but let's let's do it
this way
um okay we open
maps Okay so uh yes you can see the map
here so we talking about the British
Indian Ocean territory which is Diego
Garcia
so in the Indian Ocean in the Western
Indian Ocean which is is is incorrect
called the Arabian Sea it should be
called The Sea of sashtra but in the
Indian Ocean region western region we
have the maldis south of of the luxure
deep islands and south of the Maldives
we have the so-called British Indian
Ocean territory now this is actually an
extension of the of the lakad chos uh
underwater Ridge
formation uh so it's geographically kind
of part of the Indian subcontinent and
historically youve had Indian presence
over here uh
now
this should have been part of morius so
morius is further down south this is the
island of morus it's an independent
nation it's technically an African
nation the majority population is
Indians which is very close to the
French territory of REO so uh the
British in Ocean territory legally Etc
should have been part of macius but it
was illegally kept aside by the British
and annexed by the British and they even
picted the local people who are of
Indian and African origin and they were
expelled out of the region and then in
1973 the Americans uh built an Air Force
and Naval Base uh in Diego Garcia and I
can show it to you right here this is
the uh Air Force Base and there's a
naval base also if you look around and
I'm sure you can look around if you want
to in your own free time I don't do it
right now so why 73 why this place in
1971 the
US got a disastrous humiliating defeat
when when they lost control of East
Pakistan okay Pakistan East and West
Pakistan were a US client State a US
wasal state India victed Pakistan and
liberated Bangladesh in 71 the Americans
tried to project power here but they
were foiled by the presence of Soviet
nuclear submarines they the Americans
sent an aircraft carrier strike group
and the British also sent one but they
were they were met with the Soviet
nuclear that's why they could not bully
India they could not armist India and
Bangladesh was created so this exposed
the American need for projecting power
in this region and that's why they
acquired the bot British Indian Ocean
territory from Diego
Garcia
now I made a video about this in which I
said that this is one of the last
vestiges of Bri British colon
colonialism British colonialism still
exists today right and now the
international court of justice or
whoever it is I okay I don't remember
technically which which entity it is but
they have ruled that the British need to
get the hell out of here so the British
have agreed to do this and they've
technically transferred sovereignty of
the uh British Indian Ocean territory to
morus but they have retained the option
of of uh of controlling uh essentially
still retaining ownership over Diego
Garcia so I think it's a 99 year lease
or something that they've negotiated or
something like that similar okay I don't
remember the exact details you can look
it up but they will still retain
possession of of this archipelago of
especially the Diego Garcia at all and
the Americans will continue to control
it so it will technically be morian
territory but it will still be under the
control of the British and the Americans
so nothing really changes and a few uh
natives may be allowed to perhaps visit
or settle some or create some token
settlement or something just to you know
maintain appearances keep put on a show
but nothing really
changes so that's the
development uh when it comes to this
okay Tas is one of the many Indians who
likes to nitpick he says Mr abijit chaa
with all due respect you predicted
Kamala will win haha look who won okay
first of all I am not in the business of
making predictions I talk about
probabilities who is more likely to win
and I have said that Kamala I've said
many times that Kamala I believe is more
likely to win but I also said that Trump
will win if he kisses the ring there are
lots of nuances in these matters I don't
make predictions this is not the only
comment about this there are lots of
people who said haha abijit you made the
prediction please understand
Nuance please go multiple levels deep
the Indian look this is not the fault of
the
viewers this is the fault of the Indian
education system I'll tell you why in
the Indian education system okay let's
say you have an exam
paper you are expected to memorize the
passage in the textbook and replicate it
exactly in your
answer so you if you miss a coma if you
miss a punctuation mark If you replace
one word with another you will get one
Mark left or whatever so Indians because
of this they develop this habit of
nitpicking they look for tiny Min flaws
in something and they say yeah look at
that that's wrong this
wrong this is what you see over and over
again and it's not the fault
of my country people it's the education
system that has done this to your minds
you all you do is you look for faults
you look for Flaws but you miss the big
picture in the
process so please try to recalibrate the
way you look at things I have never made
a prediction that so and so will win I
speak about possibilities and
probabilities I am not one of those
geopolitical
analysts who goes around making
predictions I predicted this and I
predicted that and all my predictions
come true no
no I don't make predictions and many of
the say things I say may not
happen Okay so come on
please T Anonymous come on man you're
better than this come
on okay Yash Singh thank you sir thank
you so much yes G so the question is I
have some European friends who were
offended when I said that it's good for
India if PR wins what's my take on this
will been India benefit in any way with
with the Trump Victory so I've already
listed out the ways in which India
benefits okay the the thing is
that um the the world has become a very
binary place and a lot of this has to do
with the Western mentality and and it
goes back to culture religion all that a
very binary way of looking at the world
black or
white you may remember that um when the
American War on terror started when
George W Bush was the president they had
this attitude you're either with us or
against us there's no thing in between
right that sort of thing so you had to
take aide you either go in the US camp
or you the enemy and they they're going
to flatten you that sort of thing and in
other things also they they have a very
binary approach very binary Outlook and
they also have this sense of super I
ority we ruled the world we've been
ruling the world for 500 years so we are
superior and everybody else is inferior
your interests aren't important our
interests are what matters and that sort
of thing
um so they do have this attitude and
when we speak about our national
interest they say no you've got to be
Pro West I remember I was on a debate
you know there are these news debates on
on Indian television right so I was on a
news debate on
a on Republic arnab and uh the some of
the other panelists there were like two
or three Israeli
panelists on the show on that debate
there were Israeli
MPS and they were lecturing us Indians
me Arab and whoever else was of was on
the show who was Indian they were
lecturing us India has to be Pro Western
India has to be Pro Western they are
Israel MPS I I will understand if they
say that India should be pro Israel I
understand that I'll respect that
because you are Israeli and your
National interest is important to you
and that's why you are exhorting us to
be pro Israel I understand that but they
were exhorting us to be Pro West who the
hell do they think they
are do they think that they own the West
very interesting so they have this
this attitude this this uh perspective
that we don't matter our interests don't
matter we don't have agency we are like
the Native Americans what the Indian
Americans the the Native Indians
whatever they call Red Indians right no
agency we
just a subcontinent of PSIs that's how
they see us kind of you know so you know
if they get offended that's their
problem you don't have to uh be
concerned about their
feelings it's indeed TR that Trump's
Victory is going to be good for India
overall not a
tremendous lot will change but overall
it will be better for
India so yeah there there we have
it okay hardik
says hardik says Russia is making ties
with Pakistan and China does this mean
that if India goes to war with Pakistan
or China Russia will remain neutral just
like India stayed neutral in the Ukraine
Russia
war
look has India stayed neutral in the
Ukraine Russia
War uh you can say we are neutral in
this matter our prime minister has even
visited
Kiev whatever the spelling is of that
City and he has even embraced Mr
zalinski and and patted his back and and
listen to him with a very grave
expression on his face Etc we've done
that but we um look to be very
Frank we
have you could say been a we have been
very Pro India in the sense that it has
this war has kind of benefited us and
why should it not so we have um been
purchasing very large quantities
of oil from Russia at reasonably
discounted rates and we have been
refining that oil and then selling it to
the Europeans at a higher rate so it's
it's kind of benefited
us not in a small way and um we have
refused to let uh the Western sanctions
and the Western war against Russia
change our relationship with Russia so
we have maintained a very warm and
friendly relationship with Russia
despite this war going on so that is not
entirely neutral that is you could say
slightly warm towards Russia
okay uh now coming back to the question
Russia is making ties with Pakistan and
China look Every Nation looks out for
its
interest Russia currently has a certain
amount of dependency on China China is
very important for Russia right now way
more important than India China is
roughly four times larger as an economy
compared to India roughly Devo okay
don't nitpick again but you get get the
point right you get the point um so
China is really important for Russia and
China until very recently had a very
antagonistic approach towards India very
hostile approach towards India right we
our leaders did not even speak for five
years to each other that sort of thing
so the Chinese would have encouraged the
Russians
to to you know open some kind of
relationship with Pakistan and Russia
and Pakistan have been daily ding dling
with each other for quite some time um
there was this series of exercises that
happened every year Duba exercises DBA
means friendship in Russian DBA
exercises once a year between Pakistan
and mil the Pakistani military and the
the Russian military once a year would
be held from 2015 2016 onwards until
2021 if I'm not mistaken you can look up
the years and there will be plus or
minus somewhere here or there but every
year there was a set there was a durba
exercise between the two militaries one
it would be one year it would be in
Russia one year in in Pakistan
alternating right that s of thing and
the Russians even sold two or three
military helicopters with the pakistanis
and so on so there was some kind of
thing already going on but the durba
exercises have stopped they stopped from
onwards because India once again became
very important for Russia India is the
counterbalance to China definitely very
much right so I don't think the Russians
will prioritize Pakistan or India ever
if India goes to war with
Pakistan I don't think Russia needs to
come to India's rescue if there's a war
with
Pakistan Russia will technically remain
neutral they'll they'll be eating
popcorn and and watching the
annihilation of Pakistan okay with I'm
not trying to be flippant or anything
but that's exactly what will happen if
there's a war between India and Pakistan
it'll be the last last war Pakistan ever
fights when it comes to a war potential
war between India and China Russia will
be in a very tough position if India
goes to war with Pakistan Russia doesn't
have to do a thing India will deal with
Pakistan India and China is a whole
different ball game and Russia will be
in a very difficult position if that
happens thankfully India and China seem
to be on on a better track now uh there
is less likelihood of a war between
India and China but in the hypothetical
fictious scenario that there's a war
between India and China what does Russia
do
um Mr Putin will do his best to stay
neutral and actually he will stay
neutral no matter how much pressure the
Chinese put on him he will not go
against
India I I strongly believe I firmly
believe that Putin will not do a thing
that will harm India's
interests so uh we know the Russians
have been selling arms and ammunition to
both countries India and China both they
have sold the S400 system to China as
well as India very nicely balancing
things out yes
um so if there's a war between India and
China Russia will probably most likely
stay neutral
and and Putin will do his best to end
the war if there's a war that happens
and I am pretty certain that whatever
Roso we are seeing between India and
China I am pretty certain that Putin Mr
Putin has a big has played a big role in
that because it is in Russia's interest
to
have the emergence of a r i Coalition
Russia Andia China it is in all three
nations interests to have a coalition
like RC emerging Ric is the core group
of bricks isn't
it and if the three nations can find a
way to work together and
cooperate then they can
truly create an alternative to the
existing Western dominated World Order
which hurts every the nation including
these three
so I'm pretty certain that Putin has
played a big role in whatever
Improvement we have witnessed in recent
time recent months between in the
relationship relationship between India
and China and if a war happens he will
do his best to to end the war and and to
act as a mediator that's how I see it
going
okay now this is a good question by
mavin Will IND continue to improve its
relationship relations with China or
will we take a step back uh and thank
you for the birthday wishes will India
take a step back now that Trump has come
to power and once Trump uh becomes is it
takes oath and becomes the ACT actual
president right now he's the
president-elect but sometime in January
probably 21 or something he will
actually uh take oath and become the U
actual president um so once that happens
he's going to well definitely try and
steer the ship for India he's a very
that kind of person and he will
definitely want India to become way more
Pro us and and distance he will want
India to distance itself from China and
Russia as well what do we do in
that in that scenario which will which
we will come across well I'm sure Mr
Modi and his team are already hard at
work grappling with how to deal with
this of scenario I'm sure they've
already war game this out
obviously so um Trump will want us to
participate uh more strongly and play a
much more active role in the quad which
is the four nations India Japan stria
and
USA uh so that will
happen uh and uh the us obviously will
not be very pleased with the recent
convergence where
between India and China they will not
want that to become too
strong but it is in India's interests to
have multiple options we cannot afford
to permanently have a hostile neighbor
on our Northern Frontier the India Tibet
Frontier a much more powerful Nation
it's going to take us 20 30 40 30 years
let's say to come on power with
China assuming our economy keeps growing
the way it is growing right now it's a
lot of ifs and buts there but assuming
okay assuming it may take us 30 years to
reach where China is if everything goes
well then the relationship will be
different but right now we are a weaker
Nation they are about four times more
powerful than us cumulative hard power
you can't have a hostile neighbor to to
your North which is more more powerful
than you of course the neighbor has all
kinds of other
adversaries so they can't bring their
entire force to Bear against you but
still so it makes sense for us to find
ways to improve the relationship with
China it makes sense for China to find
ways to improve relationship the
relationship with us so I think there's
a lot of ground there lot
of lot of ground that both leaders both
Nations can cover a lot of stuff they
can do together we can do together and I
would be personally very pleased to see
better relations between India and China
certainly I mean we've historically
never had any issues with China right
for 2,000 3,000 years as long as China
has existed I would like to see that
happen again good relations um so it is
in our interest that we withstand
Western pressure and and push back
against western western pressure which
will seek to once again um see bad
relations between India and China we
need to keep on moving forward with our
relationship building efforts with
China and the Chinese obviously have to
reciprocate as long as the reciprocation
is there reciprocity is there we need to
keep on doing that so it's going to be a
challenge for us but I think we're going
to keep on pushing
forward uh in improving relations with
China
okay uh dinen tamang says does this
victory for Trump mean four more years
for the government of India to problems
emerging in
mizoram
um the problems aren't emerging
unfortunately the problems are there
well there these are mature problems
there aren't emergent problems the
problems have been around for a very
long time uh Mrs Gandhi Mrs Indira
Gandhi knew about the problems she took
a certain approach towards the problem
of mizoram in 1966 you can look up what
uh
approach it
took um so it's it's not an emerging
problem it's a problem that's been there
for quite some
time and because it's been there for
quite some time I expect that the
government of India and our intelligence
agencies should know exactly what the
situation is and exactly what the
solution is now obviously a solution is
a theoretical thing you have to actually
make it happen and uh certain components
of the solution may lie beyond
our uh Sovereign territory Etc yeah
so uh so overall I don't see the
pressure on us easing up and the
pressure is not coming from these rag
tag half- naked tribals okay who are
conducting terrorist activities on
against the native people of Manipur
it's not the the ragtag tribe who are
the problem of course they are the the
tip of the Spear of course and they have
to be dealt with but the person who is
wielding the spear is the real puppet
master and the real problem and that is
obviously the United States who's doing
that um so will the US go easy on India
visa Manipur project K kiland all that
no and Trump whether it likes it or not
it will happen this this will keep on
going on because this is something that
happens
when when certain agencies of the US are
involved it means that the president may
not even be involved in the whole
matter so um so I don't see that
pressure easing upon India when it comes
to the creation of kiland for Christ
they will keep on pushing for it
um so you know what they want what is
this project K cookie land for Christ is
it that they want to create a new nation
with a capital city in a nation with a
parliament that is recognized by the
United Nations they don't want that they
don't care about that they want to
create a territory in which the
government of India has no control
that's it it may still be technically
part of India on the map but they want
it to be a territory that is not under
the actual control of the government of
India and there are large parts of
Manipur where such a scenario May
perhaps
be you know played out right now so
that's the challenge we are facing I'm
using very careful language here by the
way
um so I don't think we have breathing um
you know breathing
space whatever we have to do we have to
do uh we will not get four years in
which to devise Solutions and then try
try to implement Solutions we have to
start we have to do that right now right
now now is the time there's no future
time Solutions we to find now and yeah
the solutions will take time it's it's
not going to be it's not a problem you
can solve next week next month next year
it's going to
take I mean if you have a million
infiltrators on your territory you think
it's easy to get them out it's easy to
deal with a million invading soldiers
you take them out and you deal with them
but a million invading civilians men
women children who establish Villages
and get AAR cards how the hell do you
deal with
that that's the conundrum we are facing
in a lot of that has to do with mizoram
allegedly so look the government of
India has to find the solution that's
why we elect them and that's why we pay
taxes come on deal with this and find a
solution
okay
um okay some comments I shall not put
them up over here but I shall okay mlen
says Trump Will said he will stop the
genocide in Bangladesh can he do that
can we take some action against
Bangladesh now Trump has not said that
he will stop the genocide in Bangladesh
he has said he is he said he strongly
condemns the barbaric violence against
Hindus and other minorities in
Bangladesh and I'm sure he can apply
sufficient pressure on the government of
Bangladesh on the on the not the
government of Bangladesh but the
illegitimate Muhammad yunus regime he
can apply sufficient pressure on that
regime team to essentially stop the
genocide the pograms that are happening
against Hindus right now that he
certainly can do so I think that he will
do that he will do I'm sure the first
time Mr Modi and Mr Trump speak after he
becomes the
president after he takes the O of office
they're going to discuss this I'm sure
they'll discuss it even before that so
um that will definitely happen can we do
something about it we can't right now
because this is the US wasal State this
is a US client State you do something
the Americans will you know throw a
tantrum throw a fit and they'll they'll
do things that will not be pleasant for
you so we can't do much ourselves right
now but we can certainly use the good
offices of our friend Mr Donal Donald
Trump and uh have him intercede so you
see it it kind of makes us look very
weak right India we are so weak we can't
even intervene in Bangladesh
that is not the
case we there are only two
Nations or three nations let's let's say
three to be more realistic there are
only three nations on the planet that
are more powerful than India the US
Russia
China No Other Nation is capable of
challenging India
militarily that's how powerful India is
that's the good news
the bad news
is the other good news is that Russia is
our friend we have absolutely no um no
problems with
Russia no conflicts of any kind with
Russia that's the good news number two
so that leaves us with the US and China
the bad news is that the US and China
have proxies that surround us and that's
why we cannot take action against those
proxies East Pakistan West Pakistan are
us proxies Nepal is is kind of one foot
with the Chinese one foot with the
Americans right um Sri Lanka well kind
of kind of controlled by America to some
extent uh uh when it comes to Burma
civil war between the US and China going
on there and when it comes to Maldives
pro-china so we are essentially
surrounded encircled by proxies of the
two most powerful
two powerful Nations that are more
powerful than us and that's why we look
like we are helpless in the subcontinent
if we had if if those Nations the US and
China not did not have proxies in the
subcontinent we would be able to do
whatever we wanted but that's not the
case uh so right now we can't take
action against Bangladesh but we can
certainly have Mr Trump do something
about
this
right um
RMS says is the Indian economy
performing poorly I saw some reports
saying this uh it depends on who you ask
if you ask certain Indian journalists
they'll say everything is performing
poorly nothing is going well with the
country but I think if you look at the
actual numbers GDP numbers and all I
think we are doing reasonably well we
are doing actually more than reasonably
well so I'm not concerned when it comes
to the Indian economy we are the only
large economy major economy that has a
zero chance of recession we're going to
be growing at a very good rate if all
things if if nothing goes wrong for the
next 20 30 years so I am not concerned
when it comes to the Indian economy I'm
concerned about the various geopolitical
pressures that the Americans and others
would want to apply on us to impede and
our growth that's the
problem SS masus
says Alliance on Pakistan China
Bangladesh Coalition and Iran Turks same
with help Pakistan for military against
India and Taliban Vietnam against
America and India never won Pakistan for
nuclear um
um I I apologize but I'm not able to see
the question in this
and um yeah okay I I'm sorry I did not
get
it AA belar says people are saying that
Trump will repeal the 22nd
amendment is it really possible to
change the constitution of the trifecta
and thank you so much AA 22nd Amendment
really
Will trump repeal
that look I haven't seen any any any
report that says that Trump will repeal
this 22nd Amendment the 22nd amendment
is that it it limits the the uh each
American president to having maximum two
terms every American president each
American president can be
elected twice at most no president can
have a third term essentially that's
what the 22nd amendment is now how old
is Trump let me just check quickly on
Google Trump age Trump is 78 years old
good
Gods so look by the time he's done he's
going to be
82 at the age of 82 does anybody have
the ambition of being president for four
more years I think it's very unlikely so
I don't know people if you ask the de
Democrats they'll say that Trump is the
worst person that has ever lived on the
surface of the planet and he's going to
destroy the Constitution he's going to
destroy Liberty he's going to enslave
everybody and you know they'll say He
he'll do he the worst human being ever
the Democrats um they've kind of lost it
many of
them like I said the the the West is a
very binary looking you know their their
approach their perspective is very
binary that's why you have only two
parties in the US two parties that
matter the Democrats and the Republicans
so you either hate or love love or or
hate there's nothing in between um for a
lot of people so I don't think Trump
will repeal the 22nd amendment I think
it's a good amendment to have it's a
good uh thing to have that
every president can be president only
for two terms at most otherwise you will
have dynasties which we still have right
it's the first this
election uh that we just
saw in the US it's the first election in
I don't know how many decades where you
do not have a very you did not have a
Clinton or a bush or a Biden who was
running for
president the first election in God
knows how many years minimum 20 years
probably
more uh so even with the 22nd amendment
we have such problems happening they
know dynasties are running in the US so
I think the 22nd amendment is a good
thing for that country and I think other
nations should also consider having
something like that so I don't think
Trump is going to do that I I think it
is very uh rather unlike
rather unlikely for that to happen
now
um GM soad says Will trump try to
dismantle the Deep State since he has
already wowed to do that multiple times
this may lead to another
1963 you mean JFK which is 1963 uh Will
trump try to dismantle the Deep State
look you know the previous election the
2016 election he won that election on
the promise of what what was the promise
he made he will that he will drain the
swamp what swamp Washington DC the Deep
State the entrenched Elite who are
unelected which means a deep state right
that's the that's the agenda he had
espoused that's the well that's the the
desire he had expressed that that's what
I want to do obviously he was extremely
unsuccessful in doing that he could not
do a thing think about the Deep State uh
do you blame him for not succeeding I'm
sure he
tried but do you think so that tells you
how powerful the entrenched Elite
establishment is US president can't do a
thing against them so do I think that he
will try to dismantle the Deep State
this time around I think he will not do
any such thing this time around he's
going to stay quiet he's going to have a
very specific clear agenda of what he
wants to achieve and he's going to work
on that and he's I'm I'm I'm pretty
certain is going
to refrain from stepping on the toes or
stepping on the tail of the deep
State I think he has he has got a couple
of warnings already through those
assassination attempts it's very clear
that now he knows what he can do and he
knows where what he should stay out of
and I don't think he's going to try and
once again joust against the Deep State
this the Deep State this time and we
know what happened s when you go against
the Deep State like you mention here JFK
1963 and I
remember I don't know how many few
months ago I had said that you know uh I
had said this on some of the live
streams that I I thought that Trump was
very fortunate that he did not get 1963
during his first term in
office and I also said there was a
chance that something might have
somebody might try something on him and
it actually happened a couple of times I
think there were three ination ands
against him the first one was where they
almost took him out it took out a chunk
of his
ear okay okay let's not talk about uh
assassination attempts anymore anurag
says Pelosi got her 20th term Nancy
pilow you have no idea how long that
lady has been in in essentially in
positions of
power um let's let's let's go to Google
and search for Nancy
okay one second uh give me a second we
go to Google and we search for Nancy
Pelosi I'm going to show you something
interesting so here we are okay I'm
sharing my screen and we go to nany P
see we go to images okay there she is
this is fine but how about
JFK so here is Nancy Pelosi with John F
Kennedy she attended JFK's Inauguration
in
1961 that
is that's how long she's been
around and she's got her 20th term so
what can I say what can I say
congratulations Nancy G enjoy your 20th
term um
okay honey says you say that Pakistan
will break up in a few years Pakistan is
an artificial temporary Nation yes but
uh why would the US ever lose its
interest in Pakistan because it's the
only way to counter India Sai might need
the
nukes technology if Iran ever develops
nukes well you make a very good point
here so the answer to that is that
Pakistan will break in a few years which
could be 5 years which could be S 30 7
years as long as the United States needs
Pakistan as a counterbalance to India or
for any other purpose Pakistan will
still will continue to
exist um so that's that's the situation
that's simply a fact that we have to um
deal with Pakistan will continue to
exist as long it as as long as it has
some utility for either the us or for
China
the Saudi Arabia Saudi Arabia is not
powerful enough to prevent Pakistan from
breaking breaking up if it is breaking
up but the US and China can prop up a
military regime in Pakistan so it's
either the us or China that has to
support the military regime for it to
continue
existing the moment that support
evaporates Pakistan
disintegrates it's going to dis
integrate but yeah Pakistan is valuable
it's a very valuable piece of real
estate it's a Val very valuable
territory very valuable military
professional military yes not as good as
India obviously we know that they'll be
squashed by us if they go to war but
fact the fact but yeah they have nukes
and that's that's a valuable asset to
have a good place to have it so as long
as the US needs Pakistan Pakistan will
well limp on and and continue to exist
that's just the fact
okay John says why did Trump make uh JD
Vance the vice president and not
vac yeah initially you know a lot of
people were surprised but this guy vac
he's such a good speaker so so
energetic whatever room he walks into he
is the smartest guy in the room right
and and he can answer any question he
can deal with any kind of person he's
empathetic IC he can he can diffuse
situations he can disarm uh people who
are trying to attack him and so on so
why JD Vance why not
VC so initially a lot of people were
surprised but after seeing how JD Vance
has performed in interviews and podcast
and how he has dealt with various
situations and all now it's becoming
clear that Trump has made the right
choice there's a significant difference
between the two
persons JD Vans and and vivac Vac is
extremely high energy
rather a little bit of hyperactivity
with when it comes to v he's he's
definitely matured a little and toned it
down but it's still there and and he he
is hard to relate with for for most
people because he's clearly so highly
intelligent it's like can you relate
with someone like Einstein for example
you know I'm just I'm giving a very
asymptotic solution here but it's hard
to relate with somebody like that JD
Vance is way more down to earth he's way
more approachable he's more way more
relatable despite being a very rich guy
and very intelligent guy himself but the
way he puts himself across is very
different from what VI does
secondly whether you like it or not skin
color matters religion matters JD van is
a white guy married to an Indian but
he's a white guy and he's a Christian
vac is not only a brown guy of Indian
origin he's also a Hindu very bad very
bad very very bad Hindus
look the Republicans are mostly
conservative
Christians
and
this is this
controversial but isn't isn't it a fact
Christianity is an exclusivist and
supremacist Rel
religion Christians
believe that if you don't accept Jesus
Christ you go to
hell right which means all Hindus will
go to hell and the superior way is the
way of Jesus Christ and everything else
is inferior it's a supremacist religion
it's an exclusivist religion I think
there there's no controversy in that
every Christian believes that their
religion is superior
and all other religions if you don't
believe in in their religion you are
essentially going to go and taste
Hellfire and they believe that Hinduism
is a religion of what worship
of demons or whatever they call whatever
they say there was a guy who even said
that to VI ramasami on his face that
Hinduism is a religion of devil worship
then VI is is is being has been forced
to portray himself as a monotheistic
Hindu hasn't he
so VI is in a difficult
position and and choosing him as the VP
candidate would have been from Trump's
perspective not a good move he wants to
have a vice president who is acceptable
to the broadest majority of Republicans
WC is a great guy but he's polarizing
and many Republicans especially the the
ones who are um
Christians conservative Christians they
would not find Vic acceptable and for
that reason Trump made the right choice
and chose JD van as the
VP and JD van comes across as a as kind
of you
know overall Hees he he does better in
media interactions and all that compared
to to Vic VI he kind of is hard to
relate with for most people is way too
intelligent for most people to to feel
comfortable with JD van has that you
know that easy uh friendly kind of vibe
that vivik kind of lacks it's not viv's
fault he's just that kind of person so
overall I think Trump made the right
choice whether you like it or not I mean
we would have liked to have an Indian VP
but I think most Indians did not want to
have an Indian V Indian president Kam
Kamala right we don't most Indians did
not want her to be president despite her
being half Indian so so Vic perhaps will
get some kind of position in the Trump
cabinet perhaps depends on Trump he Vic
is going to have to lobby for it hard
now he's going to have to go to
Trump and
sell what he can do for
Trump and that's just how it is that's
that's the position VI finds himself in
he should do it and I'm sure that Trump
will give him some kind of meaningful
position in his cabinet that will allow
Vic to prove himself if whether he has
the right whether he's made the right
stuff or not because Vic is a very
ambitious guy really ambitious guy and
he certainly has an eye on
2028 so 28 is going to be interesting
it's way too far ahead but 28 you're
going to have van because Trump will be
done after two two uh two stints in
office so you will have a new Republican
president presential candidate it could
be Vance it could be viac Tulsi gabard
is a big strong
Contender you know she could end up
being the first female US president she
certainly is made of the stuff that
Kamala lacks so it's going to be really
interesting really
interesting
okay okay nikel asks what exactly is the
Deep
state right what is the Deep state
how do I Define the Deep state is the
question look first of all I think we
agree that Joe Biden Jo Biden wasn't
running the country these past four
years we I think we all agree with that
I think we can also agree that
Kamala doesn't have the intellectual
heft to run a nation so Jaiden wasn't
running the country neither was Kamala
but the US still somebody was running it
right somebody was administering it
whoever is there behind the scenes so
that
is something that kind of gives us some
kind of answer but there is some kind
of grouping of people or whatever you
want to call it that that runs the
country even when the president and the
vice president are are well incapable of
running the
country now
um so the Deep State essentially is an
extra
constitutional
electoral Power Center in the
US extra constitutional extra electoral
extra
Democratic
they these people in power small
grouping of very powerful people they
have no constitutional position they
have they have never been elected and
they don't get they don't their power
doesn't come from the Democratic process
their power comes from something else so
that's the Deep State they
are a a number of people we don't know
who they are but they do exist who
control everything in the US who control
the entire country probably the the
industries and all that you know the
military industrial complex and all that
and one of the answers you can could
could lie in the question which some
people can may have asked as to who are
the
shareholders of the Federal Reserve the
Federal Reserve is the Reserve Bank in
the United States and unlike the Indian
RBI which is owned by the government the
US Federal Reserve is privately owned
and no one knows who the shareholders
are that's kind of classified so maybe
that could give some
answer um so yeah that's what the Deep
state is it is probably a small group of
people who are incredibly powerful and
who actually own and run and rule the
United States the president is just a
figurehead just a puppet whether he or
she is capable of ruling the country or
not doesn't matter the country is going
to still be ruled it's going to still be
run and that's what the Deep state is
and that's what they do and so
on um okay
arush says how to study the Far East of
India the so-called Northeast in detail
some books you'll suggest maybe you must
make a weekly podcast in the Far East
well look I can't think of any book off
the top of my mind because I've read so
many books that they all get mixed up in
my mind okay so U
um how to study the far how to study any
region in
detail it helps if you go there but if
you can't go there you to read books so
I I don't right now I don't remember you
know the study there are a number of
books in the history of Assam the
history of Manipur and so on uh history
of Burma also is important to to read
because it's kind of see the Indian
farest is geographically part of what we
call Southeast Asia okay it's our chunk
of Southeast Asia the same way that
Jammu Kashmir ladak Etc are our chunk of
Central Asia we are a gigantic Nation a
whole subcontinent um so what you should
do is let's say go to Amazon and find
search for books on Assam search on
books on Manipur and buy two three books
that are the most highly rated with lots
of reviews and ratings
and four plus star rating or something
that's that's how we could approach and
you can look at Journal articles and all
that's what you can do and it'll take
your time but that's how you approach
the study of any subject all right now I
can't remember any the names of any
books uh some of the books I remember
are not worth mentioning or I could
mention them if you want to study
Manipur one of the most infamous books
for the study of Manipur is by uh one of
the
enemies A lady called Ethel Ethel Ethel
St CLA grimswood her husband was the
political agent in Manipur in
1891 and he was taken out by the uh by
the Manipur uh armed
forces and that's what kind kind of led
to the Ango Manipur War which Manipur
lost and that was the final nail in the
coffin of the sovereignty of Manipur so
this lady Ethel St CLA grimswood she
wrote a book about Manipur which is
obviously written from the perspective
of an enemy it may be you know kind of
flattering in some ways and all but come
on it's it's your enemy who wrote that
so I would not recommend that book but
I'm sure there are lots of good books
about Manipur one of the good books
would be the chal
kumabati the chronology The Chronicles
of the kings of Manipur which go back
about three and a half thousand years
and so on but yeah just just do your own
research you know and uh read as much as
you
can
okay aha good question one and a half in
saswat says what's the impact of Elon
Musk in this us election his
impact is
immense Elon Musk has made all the
difference
in this election look Elon
Musk is the richest guy in the world
most likely he's probably going to be
the first
trillionaire a guy born in South Africa
very tough childhood abusive father and
so on comes to the us as an immigrant um
enrolls for a PhD in physics I think and
drops out after two or three
days and uh becomes an entreprene rur
and ground break breaking path breaking
entrepreneur and uh one of the
founders of PayPal and so much more he
does right than there Tesla the SpaceX
and all that
um he is uh the owner of the most path
breaking groundbreaking space
exploration company rocket company ever
he makes the most powerful Rockets he
has revolutionized everything but and
you know what he's an extreme extremely
ambitious
guy
and the problem he faces is that he's an
immigrant he was born outside of the
United States which means that he can
never uh he can never become the
president of the United States once
again I'm checking something out that's
why I'm looking here yeah okay so I put
this tweet out and let me put let me put
that on the screen the Tweet of
mine so here's the Tweet okay you can
see it now so the question that was
asked is the same question you were
asking here what was the biggest factor
in Trump's election Victory and my
answer was Elon Musk was the biggest
factor in Trump's election Victory Elon
Musk is a is a man who can never be US
president because of Article 2 Section
one Clause 5 you can look it up but Elon
Musk can possibly become even more
powerful than a US was president and I
and I ask you guess how and Trump owes
him big time so that's what I said today
and let me now kind of elaborate on
that um a guy like Elon Musk is who's
extremely ambitious he would have loved
to be president right but he can't so
what he can do is become the kingmaker
how did he become the kingmaker by
spending $44
billion he spent an amount of 44 billion
to become the kingmaker and he acquired
Twitter with that sum of money so he
buys his Twitter he renames it rebrands
it to
x.com he was the original owner of
x.com and he turns Twitter into a free
speech platform Twitter was very badly
censorious it used to censor everybody
block people at the whims and fances of
Vijaya Gade right my Twitter account was
was Frozen for years for the longest
time I was stuck at around 60,000
subscribers like 2 three years not a
single subscriber was added and on two
occasions Twitter deleted my my
followers on one one fine day I wake up
in the morning and I see exactly 20,000
subscribers have been wiped out and then
a few months later exactly 7,000 once
again in the morning have been wiped out
that's what they did to me and for the
like two or three years my account was
stuck at 60 something thousand 60,000
subscribers the moment Elon Musk buys it
my subscribers start starts growing so
that's the kind of approach they had it
was very badly censored this platform
Elon Musk bought the platform turned it
turned it into a reasonably Free Speech
platform and now it's the biggest uh
Marketplace for news essentially nobody
watches Legacy news anymore nobody goes
to the New York Times or Washington Post
or BBC or whatever everybody comes to
Twitter to see what's happening in the
world in real time
right and um he unbanned Donald Trump
you know via Gade and Jack Jack dorsy
they had banned they had banned Donald
Trump they had banned his account while
he was still the sitting president
incredible I mean that tells you that
the president of the US is merely a
figurehead he's simply a puet but that's
what they did so ilon musk takes over
and he gives the Democrats oh sorry he
gives the Republicans a voice once again
they had been censored out of everything
lots of people were banned from Facebook
meta what not people had to go to
platforms like Rumble uh Trump had to
resort to creating his own platform
called Truth social I mean that's what
they did to to free speech in America
horrible so Elon Musk bought brought
Free Speech back and he gave the
Republicans a voice
again and uh eventually he decided to to
to to put his money where his mouth is
and he backed Donald Trump he endorsed
Donald Trump and he brought a bunch of
people together people like Dana white
people like J Rogan everybody they
converge together somehow and so Elon
Musk has been a GameChanger complete
GameChanger without Elon Musk acquiring
Twitter and
giving u a voice to the Republicans
again Trump would not have won this so
Elon musk's impact cannot be
overestimated
incredible impact the one single factor
that
has uh
been uh responsible for this Victory
instrumental in in this victory of
Donald J Trump okay daily dose of gaming
says okay thank you so much for the
birthday wishes so China now has two
stealth fighter jets two variants yeah
and they both look like this like the
American thing right uh have you heard
of operation Titan rain TI i t a n r a i
n titan rain Google it whenever you want
whenever you have the time this was a
Chinese hacking operation on the United
States in the early 2000s maybe late 90s
early 2000s in which they stole
tremendous quantities of American
Military Secrets entire blueprints of
fighter planes and fighter jets and
whatnot and much more all kinds of
classified data information and this
included the the the design the entire
design of the F35 I believe if F22 also
if I'm not mistaken I'm not sure which
definitely the F35 and then they came up
with the j22 or whatever they call it
and it's kind of a ripoff of the F35 and
now they have another variant of that
the Chinese so they now have two stealth
fighter jets the Chinese they recently
um revealed the second one just a couple
of days ago so yeah the Chinese have two
stealth Fighters that are fifth
generation fighter planes India we don't
have
we have a 4.5 generation fighter plane
which is not something we manufacture we
have to buy it from abroad which is the
Rafal and we are developing the amca
which will take its first flight in the
late 2020s or early
2030s um so the question is should India
buy the so 57 or the or the F35 since we
won't have any self fighter until 2032
let's say so even then we'll have just a
handful it'll be by the late 2030s that
we'll have maybe a a decent number of
the
amcas so what do we do in the meanwhile
do we buy the so 57 which is a fifth
generation stealth fighter do buy the
F35 which is supposedly the best stealth
fighter in the world fifth generation
look you buy the F35 you're
crippled I I've said this so many times
you buy an American product they can
deactivate it at a moment's notice you
are then a hostage the Australians find
found out the hard way we are no
Australia we are not a white Nation we
are a bunch of brown
people we cannot afford to buy a an
aircraft that costs 100 million plus per
piece which can be
deactivated On Demand by the Americans
we simply can't it is it is suicidal to
do that what about the Suk 57 the sukka
57 is a fifth generation fighter plane
uh has it been inducted in large numbers
in the Russian Air Force I'm not sure
about that it's definitely a decent
fighter plane we were developing an
fighter plane pack fa or something with
the Russians but the Russians were were
being very obstinate and they were
refusing to part with certain
technological aspects of the fighter
plane and all that and they wanted to
develop everything themselves without
and and not involve us so they were
being very problematic very and and
eventually we broke we we cancelled that
project the Cod development of that
fighter plane and lost a bunch of money
in the process so that's the experience
we had with Russia now they have the Su
57 which is the kind of the output of
the
project if it is good enough we can buy
it we can be reasonably sure that the
Russians won't put um what do you call
it kill
switches in the suko 57 we have had a
lot of experience using Russian
technology platforms fighter planes they
have never done this ever to us so we
can be reasonably certain that if you
buy the so 57 at least that problem
won't there won't be there will it be a
good enough fighter plane that's
something I think the Air Force experts
have to look into they have extremely
stringent standards usually so I think
they can look into this Rook um but if
if we do need to have let's say a bunch
of fighter planes in the meanwhile we
can either if if the Su 50,000 is good
enough we can buy a bunch of them bunch
of those maybe 100 let's say
otherwise if the French are willing to
cooperate we can set up a production
line of the the the the the the Gaal in
India let's say we give them an order
for 100 fighter planes with the
condition that they transfer full
technology to us including the jet
engine technology and we set up a
production line in India so it's all
about how you negotiate what leverage
you have and what you're G giving to
give and take so um I think it's it you
know we we do face this fighter plane
crunch
we I since I was like a toddler I've
been hearing that we need 34 Squad runs
but we have like what 18 20 21 whatever
that's been a perennial problem the past
10 years of the Modi government we've
only had uh what the 36 rafas that came
in that's it um something has to be done
about this so we either buy it from the
Russians or the French with the caveat
that we build it in India we set up
production lines in India and we pay for
the technology transfer but the
technology has to be fully
transferred it's it's not easy to get
technology transfers full technology
transfers from
anybody but uh it can happen if you're
willing to pay the price so we'll
see all
right okay let's see what other
questions we
have
uh MCL says is it possible that India's
Pur purposefully dumping kistan is in
Canada
uh look I can't speculate about that
anything is possible theoretically but
in actuality what is happening
look interesting but yeah I don't know I
don't know about
that okay spandan says thank you thank
you for the birday vious sir the
question is what's your opinion on
Poland's approach to counter illegal
immigration and how should India deal
with illegal immigration so Poland has a
very know there's a couple of countries
there's a couple of nations in Europe
that have a very strict immigration
approach policy very Hardline approach
no immigrants allowed or or selectively
some immigrants allowed so for example
Poland is okay with with allowing
Ukrainian refugees but they don't want
any non-white refugees okay fine fair
enough it's your country you can do
whatever you want and Hungary also has a
very strong very Hardline policy that is
anti-immigration we don't want
immigrants I think look I respect that
you don't want a certain flavor of
immigrant don't get it don't allow that
you don't want non-white people your
choice it's your country your rules I am
perfectly okay with that every nation is
a Sovereign Nation and every nation has
the right to set its own rules but my
point is immigration illegal immigration
is destroying Europe it's destroying the
fabric of society in Europe and that's a
big
problem so I think Poland and Hungary
are doing a good job of that so that's
my opinion on that good for them keep
your country keep your people safe and
allow in immigrants selectively only the
kind of immigrants you want perfectly
okay with that I'm perfectly okay with
that and and no illegal immigrants are
allowed and borders are sealed properly
and anyone who tries to come in is is is
is given a dose of the water cannon and
whatnot so good how should India deal
with illegal immigration
H yeah we have a huge issue with illegal
immigration three major kinds of illegal
immigrants in India first is the
bangladeshis we probably around may have
around 100 million bangladeshis who have
infiltrated into India and who have
settled everywhere huge problem second
ringas they have also been settled in
India brought into India and settled
rohingyas are from Burma but they've
been settled in jamu and where not I
don't know what kind of a Nation we are
we are we are more of a joke than a
nation that this sort of thing is
allowed and third is cookies the cookie
terrorists who have been flooding into
Manipur via allegedly from mizoram and
whatnot and even directly into man
we by allowing any Tom Dick and Harry to
to to come into your country and settle
down especially those who have no
respect for your culture and your
civilization you are turning yourself
into a joke and that's what India has
become today we become a
joke we are have we are allowing the
enemy to come
in they will not become one of
us they do not respect our culture over
civilization they seek to break it they
seek to destroy it and we are allowing
them to come in we are giving
them
documentation we're allowing them to
settle we we are settling them down in
in the slums in every city what kind of
a joke of a Nation are we and this is a
matter for the central government to
take some action
on
right what should India do about this
India should find a way no matter how
much it costs India should find a way to
deport every last illegal immigrant back
to wherever they came from or wherever
else not on our
territory so my question is what has the
government done this done about this in
the past 10
years I don't know if they've done
something maybe it's not visible but you
see them everywhere the illegals
everywhere it's it's open it's blatant
now so what should India do simple but
hard to do identi
ify and Deport every single
one I'm not talking about doing anything
beyond deporting them just Deport them
back to wherever they came from it's
going to cost cost us a lot of money to
do this but yeah you create the problem
you got to solve it and secondly find a
way of fixing the leaks on the border
you have the BSF and whatnot On the
Border what the hell are the BSF
doing how did a 100 million bangladeshis
enter India
who is in charge of the India Bangladesh
border the border security
Force the role of the BSF which is a
paramilitary force not the Indian armed
so the BSF the crpf ETC the Assam rifles
these are police forces paramilitary
forces these are not part of the Indian
military they don't come under the
Indian Armed Forces Air Force or Navy or
or or
Army the paramilitary forces are police
forces who wear Army like uniforms and
who have light weapons automatic
weapons but
these these things need to be
investigated because clearly there's an
element of deep corruption in this that
so many of these individuals have been
allowed to infiltrate into India so
that's what we need to do I don't know
where we are on that
but it's this country has become a joke
we are allowing having our enemies to
come in while we have Hindus from
Pakistan who are made to live in
subhuman conditions if if they're even
allowed to come into India what kind of
a joke of a country are we I mean
seriously I don't know what to
say okay
um okay RMS says population of
Bangladesh is 169 million how did 100
million come come to India in 2014
in
2014 the government of India officially
stated that there are 50 million 5 CR
Bangladesh's in India illegal
infiltrators okay official statement of
the government of India now don't ask me
for a source why don't you go go on
Google and look it up please do that do
that much Google
searcha so officially 50 million in 2014
I would imagine in the past 10 years
maybe few million more came in maybe
maybe it's doubled now or let's say not
a single person came in since 2014 we
still have 50
million so then it means that the actual
population of Bangladesh is is your
official 169 169 million in Bangladeshi
territory plus 50 million or 100 million
in India this is simple arithmetic where
did they come from they came from
Bangladesh if they had not come then
Bangladesh's population would be 169
million plus whatever whatever exists in
India it's as simple as that I mean is
that so hard to
understand
okay
um okay okay let's talk about the US
elections right Bangladesh and all uh
yeah Samar asks an interesting question
why do all American and European
celebrities
support Democrats
now that is um that's a very valid
question first of all okay it's a very
valid
question I
remember Arnold
schwarzeneger I as a kid I loved the guy
k I love I mean he played all these
match roles very masculine roles uh he
killed the Predator he was Kanan the
Barbarian um and so much more right
so the guy was born in
Austria one of the greatest bodybuilders
of all time tremendous respect for what
he did one of the and he was number one
in Hollywood as well and then he became
the governor of California on a
republican ticket right a republican
throughout but he's been anti-trump and
he's been supporting
Kamala why would someone like him do
that and why do all these other
entertainers and celebrities in the us
always support the democ the the
Democrats very few of them if any of
them would support a Republican or or or
say vote for Trump why is
that
look I'll tell you what is being alleged
in the US okay the allegation is that
they are all compromised in some way
they are they have all been trapped in
some way or the other and some videos
have been taken and some incriminating
footage Etc maybe there of them doing
certain things are probably illegal and
so that is used to Blackmail them and
that's why they are
all on board the program that is the
allegation that is very common very
widespread in the US now do we have
evidence of that I don't think evidence
has very clearly emerged but look
recently we had the Epstein thing who
apparently committed suicide and there
was a Client List which has never been
made public but which the government has
apparently so why is that not being made
public then you have the Diddy thing
right the P didd that that
fellow he also has been has been he's
now in jail if I'm not mistaken he also
has all kinds of very bad allegations
against him so you know this this sort
of thing apparently is very common in
the US in Hollywood among the
Entertainer circles and all so maybe
that's why you know the politicians may
have a lot of dirt on these celebrities
which is something that is used as
leverage and that's why the celebrities
all control all support the Democrats
that is the allegation that is WID
Spirit do I have evidence of that no
that's I'm just telling you what I've
heard
okay okay let's take this one I think
this question was Arian has been asking
for quite some time okay uh their entire
campaign was Trump versus machine and
now that they have won and have
intelligent people like musk W they try
to systematically remove the State happy
birthday thank you for the happy
birthday
um I haven't seen this Trump versus
machine thing but okay
um Al so yeah Trump has won the
Republicans have won they have
intelligent people like
musk want they try to systematically
remove the Deep
State well the Deep
State the Deep state will have will also
have a lot of intelligent people and
people who are for them and who are not
known uh if
look if the Deep state is something that
controls the entire all the resources of
the United States the entire economy all
the businesses everything then don't you
think that is way more powerful than a
couple of people Trump musk and
ramaswami and JD Vans and and and and
what Tuli RFK
junr if you can control the it's it's
like Kardash scale one kardashev scale
one means a civilization that controls
the entire energy output of an entire
planet scale two is the entire solar
system scale three is Galaxy and scale
four is whatever
universe and scale minus one is say
let's say an entire
country all the power what can a couple
of people do against you in that
situation you they
can't right so um I think it would not
be very wise for Elon Musk or Trump to
go against the Deep state
everyone knows what happens 1963 was an
example so
yeah right
um Vikram geopolitical says Pakistan
showed interest in buying S350 missile
defense system from Russia What's My
Views and thank you for the
wishes
Pakistan is a US asset it's us client
State us wasal the Americans would want
Pakistan to acquire some Russian
technology so that it can fall into
American hands so it can be kind
of reverse engineered right there was a
time when Pakistan was a Chinese client
for about a decade or so right
um and if you remember when uh the the
alleged operation against Osama Bin
Laden happened in abbotabad one of the
helicopters of the US Marines it it uh
crashed because of rotor updraft or
whatever in that compound in abbotabad
and it crashed and the Americans had to
had to destroy that that aircraft the
the the helicopter by blowing up
explosives in it and yet they could not
destroy it completely and the pakistanis
allowed the Chinese to come and uh take
samples and do whatever they wanted with
their aircraft so the Chinese are able
to acquire some kind of technological
knowhow from the ruins from the from the
destroyed
um wreckage of that
helicopter so if the pakistanis are able
to somehow acquire acquire the S350 from
the Russians if the Russians are still
stupid enough to sell it to the
pakistanis it will end up in US
hands so I don't think it's going to
happen I don't see that happening even
the Chinese will not want that to happen
so yeah after
2022 Pakistan has become once again a US
client state until 22 it was a Chinese
client State they called the Chinese and
their iron Brothers right and so on
until Imran Khan was in power or or in
office so there you have it
okay dru's game says did Trump Kiss the
Ring like I
said yes you could you can say that he
did which means that he will not do
anything that will go against the
interests of the entrenched deep
establishment of the US he will will
this time not tread on their toes he
will not walk on their tail he will stay
clear of anything that goes against the
interests of the deep State and he will
do his best to make America great again
which means make the American economy
stable make American a technological and
space fairing superpower even more than
what it is today and and try and Deport
the illegal immigrants and all that sort
of stuff mainly it's about the economy
it's about stabilizing the economy the
economy has not been doing well us right
um tremendous inflation and whatnot all
of that is what he will do he will not
try and clean up the swamp and all that
he will stay clear of that so yes from
that sense he has understood what is
allowed what is not allowed what will
get you assassinated what will be okay
so in that sense he has indeed hissed
the ring he's a much wiser Donald Trump
this time the first four years he was a
Maverick and he was not able to do
anything because he was seen as an
outsider the by the political
establishment this time
around they're going to respect him
tremendously and he's no longer an
outsider the the the US political system
is going to see him as a Colossus now
and he's going to act way more
presidential and even the international
geopolitical world leadership is going
to see him very differently this time so
his his entire Outlook approach Behavior
agenda is going to be significantly
different from what it was for first
time around with some commonalities but
drain the swamp is gone which means that
he has kissed the
ring
uh okay let's take a couple more
questions aha is good question I like I
like yes Jagdish mly asks a great
question how Will trump deal with bricks
Trump will
not uh look at bricks with a benevolent
eye he will see bricks as bad guys and
he will say to Modi you know Narendra
bricks is bad Putin bad G bad you need
to come and be our friend we need to do
business together so that's the kind of
approach he's going to have obviously he
can't force India out of breaks or
something but he's going to put pressure
look there are lots of ways of applying
pressure on our country lots of ways
project K khalistan
ETA Manipur mizoram that's one pressure
point second the kalis
terrorists in various countries the
anglosphere countries there is that then
you have all the various anti-india
assets that the Americans have in
various parts of the Indian
establishment those can be Unleashed on
demand you can have award wses you can
have farmer protests you can
have weightlifter protests or what ja
whatever protests you can you can have
all kinds of things can be Unleashed in
India there are lots of ways they have
the Americans of
applying calibrated pressure from
various angles on
India so they
will use all of that LE leverage that
they have in different ways to try and
have India become a lose member of
bricks not a core member of bricks
they'll try that they'll definitely try
for that and Trump will also try that
and it's up to us
to find a way to resist that
pressure see very interesting times we
are living through very interesting and
very challenging times for
us Vikram says Will trump be able to
stop any of the Civil Wars going on
around the world Syria Sudan Myanmar
Yemen a lot of that may be Beyond his
control like I said he will stay out of
certain
things some of these Civil Wars we know
there's us
involvement but does the US public know
that I assure you they don't
we know it here because we are right
next door the Civil War in
Myanmar it's a proxy war between the US
and China and it's spilling over into
India and they're trying to create a
Christian country all of that is being
done by the US does anybody sitting in
the us know about this do they you think
they know this know about this in Salt
Lake City Utah do you think they know it
in Richmond Virginia you think they know
about this in in bokar
Ron Anchorage no one knows about this
the American citizenry is the least
informed in the whole world probably
they don't know anything that Beyond
what's happening in their own little
town that's how it is so Trump will let
this go on unless it is something that
harms US national
interest and lot of these a lot of the
Civil Wars and regime operations are
beneficial for the US so he won't stop
that I don't see him stopping that why
would he I mean look nobody does uh
social social service in the world GE is
not about social service and and and and
doing good for the world it's about
doing good for myself for my country
that's how it works so I don't see him
doing
that
okay shaswat says thank you first of all
is Mr Trump on the way of another JFK uh
are you talking about 1963 the
assassination I hope not I I don't think
so Mr Trump is much wiser this time so
like I said I don't think he's going to
step on the toes of the deep State now
the second question is how will the
relationship between Mr Modi and Mr
Trump be in the second term is both of
them are heavily patriotic will there be
a trade and tariff
War good good question look their
personal relationship is great they both
like each other very much okay they so
they they get along very well together
and they enjoy meeting each other and so
on so on a personal level the
relationship is great but this is not
about personal relationship it's about
the interests of the respective
countries and in that that case Mr Trump
obviously has complaints about India
trade tariffs especially one of the
examples he likes to give is
Harley-Davidson India taxes
Harley-Davidson and and imposes very
heavy tariffs on the import of
Harley-Davidson motorcycles that's an
example he likes to give so he's going
to push India on that and he's gonna say
that if you do this I'm going to put I'm
GNA impose tariffs on all everything you
export to our country he did he's a very
transactional guy which is okay so we
know how it's going to be so I'm sure
our government is going to be prepared
for that uh there's going to be areas of
agreement areas of disagreement but as
long as we can uh negotiate
constructively things should work out
fine but yeah he's going to he's going
to push us when it comes to
tariffs okay um
okay n says is GT 650 overrated these
days I have no idea what that is so let
me quickly Google
that what is a GT6 6
650 one second let's let's go to Google
and we're going to try and find that
gt650 gt650 what is
that oh the Royal Enfield model thing
okay GT
650 um I not really sure is it overrated
um I'm not allowed to have a motorcycle
by the way I'm not allowed to apparently
I'm I am capable of being a very rash
driver so I'm not allowed to have a
motorcycle I don't mind having one but
I'm not allowed to so so um I don't look
into motorcycle so I don't know what the
deal is is it overrated is it great I
don't know I think if I were to have a
motorcycle I would either have one of
those you know
Choppers or something like a
Harley-Davidson
something you know um Royal Enfield I I
hear it's got a great reputation
especially in India but yeah not much
much experience with that so uh I'm
sorry but I won't be able to answer this
question in a meaningful way but yeah
I'm not allowed
to okay okay
okay uh Yash Singh says is do you think
Mr Modi Modi G is looking a bit
strong after the recent election win
after Trump's recent election win Modi G
again along with yogi G is making
Narrative of un uniting
Hindus uh look uh the recent election
win I'm not sure which one you refering
to are you referring to Trump are you
referring to harana you're referring to
2024 general elections I'm not sure
which one you're referring to but the
2024 general elections if you're talking
about that U Mr Modi did not win a
complete majority he's he's the head of
a coalition government so that doesn't
make you appear appear very strong of
course it doesn't make you appear weak
either you were able to form a coalition
government it's a third consecutive term
as prime minister of India I mean how
many people have done that so that is a
tremendous achievement no doubt but he
doesn't look as strong as it did in 2014
or 2019 2019 was the peak Pinnacle of
his power because he got a gigantic Mand
mandate on his own
right now maybe he's a slightly
diminished prime minister but still of
course he's the he's the one man he's
the man he's still the man isn't he Mr
Modi uh
so yeah that that's how it is in
politics you know times change and we
have
to understand that that times change and
we to keep in step with the
times all right all right we will take
maybe one or two questions
more um forgotten men says first of all
thank you will India and the US deepen
their technological and Military
Alliance Cutting Edge technology
Alliance as India's Workforce grows and
jobs become St scarce will visa
restrictions is on Indians look I don't
know about the the cooperation Cutting
Edge technological cooperation if we do
uh um ameliorate that strength that good
for us but it should not be conditional
you know that like if you jointly
develop technology or you buy something
from the US it should not have any kill
switches which is always always a
problem when it comes to us technology
so that's something we have to be really
careful about we as India now about jobs
and visa restrictions interesting
question right now if you want a US Visa
this is something the Democrats have
done it takes you like 782 days or
something if you are applying for a visa
from an Indian city Chennai Bangalore
Mumbai Delhi or whatever it'll take you
more than a year to get your Visa
appointment you know on average the
waiting time you do it from Beijing it
takes three days they're Del Ely trying
to slow down things and pressure
pressurize India in this manner um now
Trump made an interesting comment few
months ago on a podcast
somewhere he said that we want legal
immigration not illegal immigration we
want high quality immigrants Indians are
the highest quality immigrants with the
highest best degrees best education and
all that and indan Indians can also be
the worst quality immigrants what you
see in Canada all the all the Riff Raff
going there um so Trump said that we get
these immigrants who come in with these
extremely high qualifications we give
them an an education and then they are
forced to go back to their native
countries because we don't give them
jobs or whatever so Trump says that if
you if you get a degree from a US
University or college it should come
with a green card so if he if
he you know keeps that promise it's
going to be a complete GameChanger for
Indian students complete Game Changer
it'll be a tremendous loss for India in
terms of brain drain but it will be a
complete Game Cher for Indian students
and it will accelerate the brain drain
out of India significantly that's
something he can do he can take away a
whole lot more of our talent If he if he
wants to but you know what it's not his
fault it's our fault that our system is
so what's
the what's the acceptable polite word so
crappy that nobody wants to stay here so
yeah so let's see how that goes maybe he
will he will give a green card with with
every degree that would be a complete
Game Changer good
God okay okay let's
uh dungar Singh Johan says are the RO
shills the real
establishment well allegedly they are so
some you know some people claim that
that is the case
do we have evidence of that maybe
circumstantial evidence maybe
not the possibility exists that that's
what I would
say okay are we are we done I guess
we're done I guess we almost
done yes
sir don't talk too much about certain
things okay I'll take one final question
please ask me a good question somebody
let me quickly quickly look around
okay this is today's last question we
have crossed Way Way Beyond two hours
ual says how are how do Russia and China
see the Trump Victory and how much is
the US deep State willing to spend on
terrorist proxies okay from a Russian
perspective I think it's there's going
to be optimism uh Trump and Putin
understand each other they know how to
deal with each other um Putin will be
optimistic that the Ukraine war can be
resolved sooner rather than than later
definitely during the Trump presidency
maybe in the first half of the Trump
presidency maybe in the first quarter of
the Trump presidency okay so it's
there's going to be optimism in Russia
when it comes to xiin Ping and China
nothing changes for them maybe the US
comes even harder against China so not a
lot of optimism is going to be there in
China right now now how much is the what
about the US deep St State and spending
on terrorist proxies they use every
trick in the book and every method in
the toolkit including terrorism aren't
we aware that the Americans funded and
financed Pakistani terrorism against
India for
decades they did that in the past don't
you think they are capable of doing that
today what's project K what's cooki land
huh what's that that's terrorism against
Indian citizens right so that's your
answer that is your
answer par says was Kamala the better
option of trump
I think Trump's way more entertaining
Kamala is
just I'm I'm I'm happy Trump
one better option overall for the US for
the world for India obviously it's going
to make the us more powerful which is
which can be a problem for the whole
world in the long term but hey let's
let's have fun today shall
we all right all right I know we've got
so many more questions but I'm going to
end it here we' across 2 hours 16
minutes so uh thank you so much all of
you for attending this extraordinary
session this emergency episode of askit
the election episode I really appreciate
your questions apologies to those of you
whose questions I could not take and
once again let me remind you next week
I'm launching a very important very
interesting new podcast called
understanding America one episode per
week at least 100 episodes we're going
to dive really deep into what America is
and we're going to go Chron
chronologically about into US History to
really understand what this nation is
the most important nation in the world
today the most powerful Empire the world
has ever seen we we better understand
this country and we don't so that's what
this podcast is going to be about it
starts next week and I look forward to
your viewership in that so with that let
me conclude today's live stream thank
you so much for watching keep asking
questions keep raising your standards
and I will see you very soon in the next
live stream thank you and see you soon
bye-bye